"Friends with Brews!" What did you send me? Just screenshots. Oh, and a picture of my 90 degree
XLR cables. Okay. What is going on with all that velcro hanging off your boom arm?
Oh, the piece of velcro that's hanging down, I could take it off of there. It was in use when
I was using this as a traveling setup for work, and I would use it to lock the arm together,
you know, so it stayed folded up completely all the time. Well, right now it's just a cat toy,
dude. It is a cat toy. The cat does sometimes in fact swat at it. Right. I try to keep my cats away
from my computer equipment. Okay, we have beer that we have to talk about first. I have. We're
revisiting the Country Boys Brewing again. Got a new one this week called Cougar Bait.
And I actually already have my trifocals on, so. Trifocals? When are you gonna go to Quadra?
I just call them that. They're just readers. Oh. Any fisherman worth his salt will tell you
it's all about the bait. Lucky for you, you're holding the good stuff. An American blonde ale,
clean and crisp cougar bait is sure to help you with your catch, whatever you may be fishing for.
And we're not going to discuss any further connotations beyond that.
Wow. So I have cracked it open. Okay. I have my chilled frosty glass. Yeah. We're pouring. Yeah.
Does in fact look blonde. Here you go. It's pretty. Looks good. What does it taste like? Good.
Doesn't really say anything about any flavor notes I'm supposed to be looking for. This is American
Blonde Ale. I don't know enough about the different kinds of beers to really say but it's good. I like
it. You know I gotta talk to these guys about their website. I don't know what it is about
beer brewers and websites but they are sh*t. Absolute utter sh*t at websites. The worst ones
are the ones that don't list any of their beers. The second worst ones are the ones that list all
their beers on one page and don't have a detail one for the specific beer. The third worst ones
are the ones where the home page CSS won't load. It literally won't load and so the website looks
like hell and then when you click on our beer you just get a list of what's on tap daily, our beers
rotate often. No, you sell stuff in the store too. Why don't you show the stuff that you sell in the
store? I mean they do, but by accident I get the feeling. What a bunch of... yeah these guys...
I don't understand like who made their website. Like it wouldn't have cost any extra to just put
a little bit more information on the website. It wouldn't have cost any extra. Okay so here's my
coffee. My coffee is a trailhead roasters endless trail. It's a medium roast. By the way, look at my
cup. I like that mug. Wait, what does it say? Let me see it again. I work hard so my cat can have
a better life. Is that it? Yeah. Especially crafted to get you out on the trail. Robust all
business sort of coffee. I don't know if I'd say that. Notes of mold. That's a tall boy too. Wine,
cinnamon, and toasted rice. Very balanced and syrupy. They hold its flavor in the thermos rather
well it is good i don't can i taste the rice and the cinnamon yeah i can taste cinnamon for sure
yeah it's good it's a good coffee so i'm having that i'm also having a Zoiglhaus
so you good house it's not a tumor and this is the Zoigl weiss it's a german wheat pilsner
ammunic malts provide the light breadiness german hops and the bavarian hefeweizen yeast
strain provides the rest. Banana Esther with a light phenolic clove note. I don't know
what phenolic means but it sounds pornographic. Okay, so I'm going to open this can.
Okay, I'm giving my beer a thumbs up. I'm giving your governator impression a thumbs
down. Okay, but I want to know, well, okay Mr. Kentucky, let's hear you do it.
It's not a tumor. Oh my gosh.
not a tumor do you think that sounds German no you know one that just about
everybody can do right though get to the chopper okay this is good I like this it
looks nice hmm my beers never have a head on them I must be pouring wrong or
something no you're probably not pouring wrong I'm pouring right next to the mic
so you can hear it that's part of the problem I'm at an angle I don't think I
I poured next to the mic.
I have failed.
You are pretty amateur, Vic,
'cause you know how we do things here.
You listen.
You say you listen.
Oh wait, I forgot.
You listen to podcasts while doing 10 other things.
So you never actually know.
You never actually...
I'm surprised that you know that you listen to this podcast.
Actually, that's pretty good.
I'll give you credit for that.
You should cancel my contract.
Zeigl Weiss.
You gotta love the name Zeigl Weiss.
I still can't edit.
Wait, let me refresh this.
Log out and log back in.
Now there we go. I got it. Wow, you've got typing problems there buddy. I do. Oh that didn't work
What did you do? You did command V instead of command K. I command K. Oh
Or in in paper you can just paste it right over top of it and it that's it stinking
Yeah, but paper is such an utter
You got to admit paper kind of sucks. It does but I don't think it I don't know that this is any better
Paper is just weird. I will say both of these are a plus above iOS shared notes for podcasting. I hate them
Mmm, some of our friends like using them though
so I roll with it the one thing that I definitely like better about this than notes is the
Outlining is a lot easier. It works. Normally it works how you think it would work
You hit tab do indent and when you want to out day, you just hit return one more time
That's how all the apps in the world work except for Apple notes
Sometimes it does sometimes it doesn't or if you got it wrong, you can just do a shift tab and back it up
Mm-hmm back that thing up. Yeah, it doesn't make I don't know. I don't know what Apple notes is done and
one of the notes
One section of the notes that we have for is this the show somehow it got so host that I can't unindent
I literally can't I just had to
Push that section away and use a different section. I don't know what's going on there
It literally won't out dent but I created a new section and that section out dents just fine. Don't know why
That's Apple notes for you functional high-ground man functional high-ground and moral immoral high-ground
All right. So yeah, I like my beer. It's it's it's not the clearest wheat beer. There's some nice little cloudiness to it
It's a very good. This is a good beer
That's cool. The good beer with the shit website
But I just described half the beers I've ever drinking drinking gonna need a sound thingy. I just did
Okay. Oh, oh, you know what I got since I didn't put my mic Zeigl close enough for the pour
Now that's fake first of all, there's no ice and beer that is actually not fake I
Recorded that live in person. Oh, really? Yeah
Wow
That was actual climax moonshine pouring but see in your whiskey you might but you're right. It is not beer
Yeah, we don't put ice in our beer
No
My granny used to put salt in her beer. What?
Yeah, it's weird. Why I don't know. She just sit there with a beer and a salt shaker
She didn't drink beer to enjoy it. She was just drinking at the pound beer then I guess I don't know
Cuz she didn't really pound beer she's
She only drank it socially. Oh, I think she was actually trying to make it palatable to her have a salt
I don't know man. That's disgusting. I love my granny settle down. Okay, you can love your granny. She's still got issues
No, she's dead. Okay
There's a reason why she kept putting salt in her beer. Oh my god
Hey, I'm sure she would have liked that joke never having met her I'm positive she would have liked that joke man
that one choked me up. Okay, let us talk about the moon. The moon. Did you know
some Russians crashed a thing into the moon? Yeah, they're rubbish. We just
established that they're rubbish at the moon. We have established that they're
rubbish at the moon. Their very first flight to the moon, they crashed into it
and now they're crashing into it again. It's like they learned nothing. The wife
actually stumbled across that headline and she was telling me about it this
morning and that's when I sent it to you guys. I just found it fascinating. I
I didn't realize that the moon was of interest again.
So this moon of interest thing started
under the Trump and Pence administration.
Pence was the head of the stupid space force
or whatever they called themselves.
You telling me those two bozos
actually started something cool?
Well, I don't know if it is cool.
And I don't know if the reason why-
According to the moon, it's cool, man.
I don't know if how much of it was NASA proposing it
and they just thought they'd run with it
because it was different than what anyone else was doing.
And I don't know if you noticed,
but Trump was always trying to be as different
from his predecessor as possible.
Not just that he naturally is as different
from his predecessor as possible,
he also was actively trying to be as different
and do everything as different.
If there was any policy that Obama had tried to put in place
or did put in place, Trump was actively trying to revert it.
- Yeah, but, hmm.
- And so I don't know how much of going back to the moon
was saying, "Hey, forget about Mars, we have a moon."
Or how much was NASA saying,
"We really wanna go to the moon."
them saying, "Hey, this could look like our idea. Let's promote this." I don't know. But
at any rate, during those years, they became obsessed with going back to the moon again.
And somehow it stuck. We're still going back to the moon. Anyway, yeah, this has been going
on for a while, this moon thing. So I don't know which came first, the chicken or the
egg. I think Americans decided to go back to the moon first and then maybe Russians
did. I don't know. Somebody said, "Hey, that other country is going to the moon." Well,
those guys we're going back to the moon too and i don't know who was the original and who was those
guys copycat but one of them was one of them was one and one was the other anyway we're going to
the moon it's for all mankind in real life man except for the chinese because america and china
have a have issues with each other when it comes to space and everything else right now
wasn't it the koreans that beat us to the moon or to mars not the chinese
that was fiction i'm just saying i'm talking about real life here all right if you want to be boring
anyway i don't know i don't know what's going on there's a program called artemis there's going to
be three stages stage one stage two stage three stage two has astronauts i believe
and artemis 3 is actually going to go to the moon here is the problem though so where are stage one
and two going? I don't know. Out in the space. Okay. I don't know. I'm not sure. I didn't pay
that much attention to stage two because I know they selected a crew for it, but I didn't realize
they weren't actually going to land on the moon. They might be going to the moon to orbit it. I
don't know. I'll have to look that up. Hopefully they do a better job than the Russian automated
craft. Well, you could say it stuck the landing, but it did not stick the landing.
It stuck into the landing. Yes it did. So Vic, look, they... when's the last time you got 100%
on your math test? I'm just gonna ask you that. Well that'd be a long time ago. Right, so give the
Russians some slack, man. They probably got 99% right on their math problems, and they screwed up
the last three feet of math or something, so cut them some slack. It's not like that last three
feet is important anyway. I mean, come on. Yeah? Yeah, it's not like it matters whether or not they
they get 100% of their math right when they're sending human beings out into the cold reaches of outer space.
Mm-hmm. Not at all. They can get some wrong.
Two plus two is five, right?
Anyway, we're dependent on SpaceX for part of Artemis 3, and I'm not sure which part.
So that means that Troll Musk is involved?
Yeah, fortunately he does seem to actually have some competent people running SpaceX itself and doing the science. However...
What is Bezos's thing called? Why didn't they go that route? Blue Origin? Because apparently Blue Origin didn't have it together.
I don't know. They were candidates, but they didn't get any contracts that I know of. Okay.
Yeah, at one point Blue Origin was hyped up pretty good. Blue Origin's still going,
I know that, because there was a co-worker of mine, an engineer who used to work at Monolith 3000 who now works at Blue Origin.
Hmm. And he still has a job and they're still doing stuff. So they must think that somebody's gonna want them to do something for them.
That's cool. Anyway, I think that NASA is becoming quite concerned about the progress of SpaceX on the Artemis 3
Project and they're a little worried about the amount of time that they have left to do all of the testing that they have to do
because
Even though NASA has had some major FUBARs in its past because they hand-waved a bunch of safety
Regards and didn't listen to some engineers and then some people died
NASA still does have a pretty good testing
Culture in terms of they know that they have to test stuff before they can shoot it into space where it's fine
You know, it's real mission. Yes, and
They're a little worried about
SpaceX not having really begun any of this testing of which there are many steps many stages and
There it's never gonna go right the first time anyway, so things are gonna have to be corrected. So
originally, I
Can't remember if Artemis 3 was scheduled for 2022 or for 2023, but now it looks like it's gonna happen in 2025
Hmm NASA is still saying it could happen in 2024. My bet is unless
SpaceX gets together it will be 2025 at least. Yes. What's the matter your stuff's not shipping on time
No, I need you to stop saying 25 25. Why do you remember that great song in the year?
Mankind is still alive you did but it's just making that stuck in my brain. It's an earworm forget about 25 25 Vic
My prediction is now I have sung on the podcast and that's just horrible. My prediction is by 2030
We're gonna be up feces Creek and if we're not extinct by then we'll be extinct shortly after the way things are going
hmm
There probably still be some humans around in 2030 2030
2035 I'm saying
The fan the the creek could hit the feces or the creek could hit the fan or the fan could fall in the creek
I don't know. Oh, wow
The fan could fall in the creek and go up the creek without a pedal.
Sager and Evans in the year 2525.
I don't...
You don't really remember this song?
I remember the song.
I just, I didn't, I guess it didn't scar me emotionally the way it scarred you.
No, it didn't.
It's actually a good childhood memory.
My dad used to blast that thing.
He loved that song on an actual vinyl turntable.
Is there any other kind of turntable?
No.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
That had a pretty kicking system and on the weekends, man, he would jam some pretty good
music when I was younger and I used to just love listening to it and flipping through
his records.
Then you should be happy.
He'd never let me work the thing, but...
One thing I did like about records when I was a kid was the jackets and just holding
them and reading them and looking at the pictures while the music was playing.
That was pretty cool.
Yeah.
Okay.
Would you like to hear a sample?
Um, you can if you want to, sure.
Why not?
Why not get this podcast banned from all platforms?
It's a good thing that I self host.
I think mainly just Spotify.
Really?
Well, if we put this on YouTube, which I don't,
it would get banned from there too.
Start only for me, share play.
Oh, it wants to share play it, no.
Don't share, no, no.
(upbeat music)
♪ In the year 2525 ♪
♪ If man is still alive ♪
- They won't be.
♪ If woman can survive ♪
- No.
♪ They may find ♪
- What category of music is this considered?
- I think it would be rock.
♪ In the year 3535 ♪
- Yeah, definitely.
♪ 35, 35 ♪
♪ Ain't gonna need to tell the truth ♪
♪ Tell no lies ♪
♪ Everything you think can't say ♪
- Right, okay.
- This is your nice fade out.
- Shut it down, there you go.
Nice! - So you don't have to edit.
(laughs)
- Nice work.
- So you don't have to fix it in the edit.
- Nice.
- Let's see.
This is on a compilation of pop music.
- Really?
That's considered pop?
- 1988.
Well, that's just the first one that came up in the search.
Hold on.
Let me see.
Let me see if I can find like the actual album.
I like this beer. I'm surprised by how much I like it.
Considering I've never heard of these guys
and they have a website.
- 1969, Zagre and Evans.
- It sounds like a sixties song.
- Yeah, it does.
- Well, I'm very pleased that brewers don't have to know
anything about the internet in order to craft good beer.
- This is true.
- Hey, have you ever dealt with construction companies
or any kind of trades people, electricians, contractors,
any of those guys, somebody that wants to do a fence,
whatever.
- Generally, I try and keep them all out of the house.
I did have some roofers put a roof on.
No, no, no.
But have you ever had to schedule stuff
and interact with them and get planning going?
Yeah, the roofers.
But have you ever noticed that those contractors
don't know how to communicate?
Like they don't know,
their communication is generally terrible.
Like getting them to call you back,
getting them to, I don't know, it's always horrible.
The people that are good around here,
actually the roofers that we had have been good,
were super good.
That's what I was getting ready to say.
I don't wanna argue and say you're wrong,
But the roof job that I had done, it took a few, you know, a few appointments
and, and some conversations and some estimates and stuff like that to get
the job actually scheduled, but then once scheduled, the guy pulled up.
30 minutes early, let out a bunch of nice Hispanic gentlemen.
Right.
And in like four and a half, maybe five hours tops, they had completely
stripped my old roof and put the new roof on and then ran magnet things
through the yard to pick up any loose nails.
It was pretty epic, man.
I tried to buy him lunch and they even declined it.
- See for us, it took a little longer
because we had shaker roof and the shaker roof
doesn't have the plywood down underneath it.
And so they had to lay plywood.
- Oh, I just had the asphalt shingles.
- Right, they had to lay down plywood first
and then they could start applying the new stuff.
So it took them a little longer.
Otherwise it was the exact same scenario.
But even scheduling, it was a dream with those guys.
It wasn't the roofers that were the problem.
It's like, but I've just noticed that contractors in general,
like they, it's always some guy that wants you to message
him or something and then they may get back to you.
It's like, have you guys heard of business phones?
Have you heard of a website?
Have you heard of calling back when somebody contacts you?
Have you heard of remembering who called you
and pretending like we're not starting
this whole conversation over from scratch again?
I get that a lot with trades people
and I don't understand why.
It's like, yes, doing the actual job itself,
right is important, but the communication part of it is too, because part of getting
the job done right is having successful communication beforehand.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's weird.
Anyway, I think of them when I...
What kind of things are you having contracted?
Right now, nothing.
But I think of them when I think of the breweries and the websites, and it's like, don't you
guys understand that part of your business...
I see the connection.
Yeah.
It's like, why are you sloppy on the communication?
99% of your business is communicating to people clearly the reasons why they want your product.
I'm just glad I can fix things so that I don't have to deal with the contractors hardly ever ever
ever. Yeah I gotta get some trees ripped out though I got roots growing towards the base of my
house. Oh that's not cool. No it's not cool at all and they're very hard to kill and I really don't
want to rip out. They'll crack your... you got a basement or just a slab or what? Crawl space.
Why? There's no... we don't do slabs around here. I don't understand the slab thing. No,
I'm on a crawl space too. How do you run pipes and stuff? They just run them before the the slab is
poured. That's insane! What if they crack? What if they break? There's no way to get to them. That's
insanity. Then you jackhammer up the slab. That's insanity. Yeah, I had to do it once when I was
doing... one of my jobs in my life has been maintenance at a nursing home and we actually
had to jackhammer up an office floor to get to some plumbing underneath. I was gonna say you have
to go through the floor too. That's insanity. Just build a freaking crawlspace. Yep, we had to go
through the vinyl floor and then jackhammer up the concrete and then scoop out massive amounts
of gravel and then fix the pipe and then dump all the gravel back in and then pour new concrete and
then put down new vinyl floor. That's insane. Yeah, I'm glad I'm on a crawlspace too. We had a water
pipe break under our house one winter and I had guys come out and run me some flexible pipe.
Yeah.
But if they would have had to, I mean, it was already still freaking expensive. It still cost
me a fortune, but they basically took this drill bit that could bend and you just keep adding
sections to the drill and then you just curve it up. You just send it down underneath the front
of the house and it comes up in the crawl space and they figured out the radius of how to make
that thing bend up there and it goes boop and it pops out and the tube is going with the drill.
So the tube just pops out there and then they send a guy crawling under there and he connects everything and it still cost a fortune
I can't imagine how much it would have cost to have pretty awesome though
Oh, it's very awesome
But I can't imagine how much it would have cost if if they literally had to rip out the floor of our house
Drill through that's just insanity. It sounds like those things they use those big horizontal drills that they're using like to lay fiber optic
maybe
Conduit and stuff underground through residential neighborhoods and stuff. Yeah, very possibly
- Right, when they put in our gigabit fiber
a couple years ago when they were first putting it
in the neighborhood, I was just watching this guy's work.
It was pretty epic, you know,
'cause they've got, they've ran conduit
and fiber through this whole neighborhood.
And all you would know is that there's a hole
like every 75 feet across the back of the property lines.
And it's like, that's just amazing how they do that.
- Yep, now if you go out in your backyard
and you see a bunch of tiny vertical holes,
those aren't, that's not fiber optic.
I wouldn't stick my hand or anything else in those.
That's moles and gophers and such.
Well, in some places it's stuff more toxic than that.
But I forgot, you live in the safest place in America.
Oh boy, here we go.
No, I'm not gonna go there.
(laughing)
You've really gotta be in your bonnet
about this door lock thing, don't you?
I don't know anybody that thinks that it's--
Can I state for the record
that they are never intentionally unlocked?
I know that, no, I totally understand that.
But what I'm saying is for you to say
that it's a cynical worldview to think
that you have to lock your doors, that blows my mind.
I don't know anybody around here that would think,
"Oh my God, I'm so dark."
I just think that the odds, first of all,
there's always somebody here at night
unless we're traveling, in which case then, you know,
I've got my cameras and I've got security lights
and stuff like that.
And then I make sure for a fact that the doors are locked.
So there's always somebody home at night.
And the odds of somebody in this neighborhood coming and, you know, going up into the house
and doing whatever during broad daylight are pretty slim to none.
Well, they're slim here too, but occasionally you'll have waves of home invasions.
Yeah.
And why make it easy for people?
Oh, I get that.
I don't disagree that ideally the doors should be locked at all times.
I've had a guy try the front door before.
Really?
And that was it.
Yeah, and once he realized it was locked, he moved on.
See, I've never had that.
Yeah.
Not here in this neighborhood, anyway.
I used to have it in places I used to live in the past.
The only thing that's ever happened here is like I said, sometimes I don't even know if
their kids from this neighborhood or kids from the other neighborhoods, but sometimes
at nighttime they'll go through the neighborhood looking for cars that are unlocked to see
what they can find in them.
Right, exactly.
And that same theory applies with houses to some other people who are willing to do that.
That's the point.
Like I had a neighbor whose stuff was stolen out of his car and he's like, "Well, I don't
want to lock my car.
I don't want to be one of those people."
He was just like you.
that's too cynical and I'm like, well, guess what?
My stuff's still in my car and your stuff's gone.
So how do you like that?
- No, the car in the driveway, I would lock.
Most of the time my cars are in the garage,
so I don't worry too bad about that there.
In fact, when they're in the garage,
I actually leave the keys in them.
Which is probably not a great idea,
but they're behind the garage door, so.
But if for some reason I'm parked in the driveway,
they're locked.
- Ronnie was like, well, if they wanna break in,
they're gonna get in anyway.
Yeah, but there's two different types.
There's types who'll just try it
and they might steal something,
and there's types who are break-in.
Break-in guys are always gonna break in, I know that.
I totally understand that, that's not the point.
You shouldn't make it easy for people to get in.
- Yeah, I will say though,
that I actually agree with him that a visible camera
is gonna do you a lot more favors
than even the locked door will,
because as soon as they see that, they'll move on.
- Why, why?
- Because they know they're on camera.
- But Vic, if you're a guy who's determined
to break in anyway, you'll wear a mask or something.
They know that people have cameras now.
- I guess, but again,
during the daytime,
it's pretty slim to no odds.
And we're here at night.
- Yeah, it is. It's true.
It's true. It's just why make it?
Yeah, but you don't wanna be in, you're also asleep.
Like there are times at night
where somebody could literally walk in the house
and walk up to the bed and I wouldn't freaking notice.
Why do that? Why take that chance?
- Now that I would actually know
because I've got HomeKit automation rules
that if the front or back door opens between like I think I set it for midnight to dawn something
like that if either one of those doors opens that every single light in the house comes on yeah I
have that now too and the outside the house too I have that now too but yeah that's pretty cool
I even thought about making the home the home pods play something very loudly but
I was concerned that like a lot of the times the home pods kind of fail in in the home kit
automation scene and like playing scenes and stuff like that so I was afraid that if I put that on there and then
That failed to play then it might fail to not turn on the lights, too
So no you just have the home pod last but you're more likely to have the opposite problem where the home pod just starts playing
In the middle of night, even though nothing happened. Oh
Yeah, that'd be bad, too
I don't know so far the lights are never turned on in the middle of the night when nothing happened, right?
anyway, the thing is is that like
Locking your doors so easy. Why not do it? It just oh, I agree keeps the people who are gonna try a door out
Like I said, it's never an intentional thing. It's always just because somebody was careless and not attentive enough
I'm thinking more about Ronnie's like but the cameras will stop him, but he doesn't worry at all about the doors
Why not do the doors - that's that's easy. Like you can control what you do
You can't control what the bad guy does, but you can control you. Why not control you?
Well to be fair to Ronnie, I think he said it was his family that was leaving the door unlocked
He wasn't even home. So I know but why not? That's the only thing I've ever that's the only thing I ever say to my family
Hey you guys you've got to get your act together and not do that. That's the only thing I say like it's not like I'm hounding
Them constantly. Yeah, you don't dress appropriately. I don't like the way you pull in the driveway
There are some men like that, but I think it's okay to say hey guys, can we just keep the freaking doors locked? Maybe?
Yeah, that's fine. I don't know. Anyway, it's not that I think that you guys are wrong saying the odds are super low
I hundred percent agree with that. What blew my mind was when you said, "Well, if I lived in a neighborhood where I had to lock my doors, I'd move."
Because that's every neighborhood, Vic.
No. In my lifetime, Scott, I have lived in neighborhoods where I knew I had to lock the doors.
Even in broad daylight, people will come in and they will steal your shit.
Right, but you're conflating that with my situation, which is not the same as that at all.
Yeah.
Well, I think it's just in part the way you guys were responding, and granted it was in text only,
you know, we didn't have the benefit of seeing faces and hearing voices. In text only, some of
your and Clay's responses seemed like you guys were pretty paranoid, man. And I think we were
just responding to that. Why would you leave the house and go to work and have your doors unlocked?
That's crazy to me because somebody will try it and they'll get in it takes two seconds to walk in and steal something
It's that fast. Even if you see him, there's nothing you can do. Yeah again, it's never never
Intentional and the wife's always here too. Right, but you were you guys were amazed that we would feel
Nervous about leaving our doors unlocked and being completely elsewhere and not able to get there
Yeah, that seems normal to me, man
I could see that it is the proper best practice that we should always do
But, as far as the things I worry about in my day-to-day life, if we forget to lock the
door one day, that's pretty low.
Yeah, I guess the way it came across was you and Ronnie are lax.
And I feel like Ronnie's way more lax than you.
He was just like, "Don't f***ing care, dude!"
That's how he came across.
And I just think that's crazy.
Maybe I'm wrong, maybe that's not how he comes across, but you know how it is.
It's like his AppleCare thing.
Nobody ever needs AppleCare, that's a waste of money.
Meanwhile, all of us have made use of paying for AppleCare and having it pay off for us before
That's how it came across to me. No offense Ronnie. I know you're listening, but sometimes you're blase about the weirdest things. Okay
I'm just saying it like it is!
Are we done insulting and alienating our friends now?
I'm done for now. I'll get back to it later.
We love you, Ronnie.
We do love you, but Jiminy Christmas, sometimes I don't understand it.
I don't know if I would live in Las Vegas and never worry about theft.
That one I don't buy, I'm sorry.
I know he loves Vegas and he thinks it's progressive, but Vegas is like anywhere else, they have
issues.
And I for sure think there's people who would steal stuff in Vegas.
Yeah, but I think he lives like on the outskirts of town, and I know he said the closed gate
community too as well.
Yeah, yeah.
They've got gates and all that.
He's one of the muckety mucks.
A muckety muck.
He's one of the rich...
See, there you go again.
Well, I'm just, hey...
I'm gonna switch into disclaimer voice here for a second.
The opinions being expressed are Scott Willseys and Scott Willseys alone, they do not reflect
views and opinions of icons.
Why would we have to say that when it's the words coming out of my mouth and not yours?
I think that should be obvious.
I'm distancing myself.
Mm-hmm.
I get that.
Because you're running for Kentucky something.
I don't know what.
What are you running for?
I'm running for remaining to be Ronnie's friend.
You can't be replacing Mitch McConnell because you have to practice your oh,
my goodness. You have to practice your mini stroke.
He needs replaced so badly.
He needed replaced even before he had strokes every 10 minutes.
Is he having strokes?
It wasn't it him, was it Mitch McConnell?
It could have been. I don't know.
I don't follow McConnell's the droopy dog looking guy, right?
He looks like a turtle, man. Yes.
McConnell, he just stood there.
They were having a press conference and all of a sudden he just went nowhere
He was like gone and his aid comes up and says do we want to move on right now?
And they had to he just disappeared for like five minutes. He was just out. I
Wonder if he really did have a stroke. He probably did
Hmm
Yeah
Huh, yeah his aides were like, "Shut the lid and this looks like it's gonna be a long one"
And then he replied with "Are you also experiencing comprehension deficiency?"
[laughter]
I don't think he can sound that sophisticated.
I wonder about him. Like, I seriously wonder, is he just...
I don't know, I wonder about a lot of politicians, like, are they really just that out of touch and selfish and...
Because sometimes it seems like the things that some politicians do is, like, actively evil.
And you wonder, are they really actively evil? Are they just getting paid and they're just selfish and they're all about...
You know, you wonder, what is the...
What is really behind this guy? And Mitch McConnell is one of those people that I wonder, what is really behind this guy?
Right.
But I don't worry about it enough that I bother to delve into it and do research and interrogate his family.
Probably I would get arrested if I tried to interrogate his family, I would think.
I'd go to Mitch McConnell. I'd be like, "You can start talking anytime." And he wouldn't. He'd just be on there in a coma.
All right, so we're going to the moon. What else you got? You like your beer? I do like my beer.
Oh, would you drink that? How does that compare to the other old boy or country boy or whatever you had?
I need to drink a few more of them to really compare the two. I like them both pretty good
I'm kind of inclined to say I think I like the what was last week's shotgun weddings that what I was called
I think it was I'm kind of inclined to like it a little better, but I like them both. They're both good. Okay good
That's good. That's a good problem to have
I mean not knowing which one you like better is good problem to have the vanilla notes in the shotgun wedding were pretty nice
That does sound really good. Yeah, that one sounded good. I think in general
I like that style of beer better than I like the one you're having now, but for some reason in the summer
I kind of like the lighter ones most. Yeah
Well, you should check and see if maybe these have made it some stores in your area. I don't think so
I've never seen them. Let's put it that way
There are some beer specialty shops though that get beers from all over that may have some so yeah
I actually I'll have to look well
I do know that the see the reason I learned about this company is
on a recent trip a few weeks back the wife and I took a trip to Gatlinburg, Tennessee for a couple of days and
We went into it's a chain pizza place. I don't know if you guys have it out west or not called
Have you ever heard of Mellow mushroom?
They're not a huge chain like, you know, they're not like the Papa or Domino's or Pizza Hut or anything like that
But they are a chain
They're pretty good our nearest one at home is like 50 miles away
So by the time I went and picked one up, you know and got it home. It would be all cold
So when we're down there there there's a couple of them in the area
so we usually like to grab one of those pizzas when we're down there and
I we went in and placed it to go order and we were just sitting at the bar and
She was having water with lemon and I was having a beer and I was looking at their selection of craft beers
And I noticed that they said they had one from Georgetown and the guy was talking to me about it
And he said it's actually very very popular there. So it's at least as far away as Tennessee
Did you guys get the stone baked pizzas? Are you looking up the mellow mushroom? Yeah, if it's us they're stone-baked then yes
No, some I'm getting the impression that some are some aren't but maybe they all are. Yeah. Yeah, I guess they all are
I don't know. I don't know much about their baking process. I just know that no, it looks like it looks like they are
We we stumbled in there one time to grab a pizza
Just because we felt like having pizza and we were like, this is really good pizza
And so it's kind of become a tradition whenever we go down there. We have one. They don't look bad
I was getting ready to say do they got pictures? I'm going to disgust I
Don't know why
Why people hate pineapple on pizza and it's such a religion to hate it. It's unnatural
This one called Pacific Rim has red sauce base of mozzarella ham bacon caramelized onions pineapple and jalapenos
I would love that that sounds amazing
I love that this website has a button that says do not push
Where did you see that go back to the home page? I'll try
First I have to wait for the pizza. All I see is one that says order online. Oh do not push push it
Oh, that is so cool
Please enable flash to surf the web. Oh my god
Wait, if we had Flash installed, would something be happening there?
I think so.
I think this actually does use Flash still, Vic.
I'm not gonna install Flash to find out.
No, no one does.
Let's see, let's see.
Let's see, what were you looking at?
The menu?
Which pizza were you talking about?
I was looking at Pacific Rim.
Mellow red sauce base with mozzarella ham bacon caramelized onions pineapple and jalapenos
that all sounds fantastic to me with the pineapple man so i have made this very pizza except
for i'm not a big hater of it but i don't really like it except i didn't caramelize
my onions and i didn't put jalapenos on next time i'm gonna make it this way i'm gonna
caramelize my onions and i'm gonna put jalapenos on there what does that exactly mean caramelized
onions that basically you just saute them in a skillet or something yeah basically yeah
Yeah, okay, yeah.
You get a little bit of brown on there
and it gives onions a good flavor when you do that.
What we usually get is half and half veg out
and mighty meaty.
Let me guess, you're the mighty meat guy.
Always.
Let me say something to you, Vic.
I used to be,
Yes.
Years ago, I used to be hardcore.
I wanted the meat pizzas.
I wanted the pepperoni, I wanted the,
branch out a little bit, you will not be sorry.
Yeah.
Pizzas have barely any meat on them now. I have been branching out a little bit lately like a lot of the times I'll have
Sometimes I'll have some green peppers
Kind of rare but on occasion I really love mushrooms. I really love mushrooms, but you're adding stuff to the meat pizza
yeah, but not the meat lovers pizza like my current favorite pizza is a
pepperoni mushrooms and jalapenos
Yeah, and that is good
I'm just there is still some meat on there and the pepperonis, but you know, it's not just a meat lovers, right? Yeah
Yeah, I'm just saying believe it or not. There are some amazing pizzas. They have no meat whatsoever on them
Yeah, you might not believe that and those are nice-looking pizzas though. Oh, yeah
They're good-looking. Yeah, this looks like a pretty good chain. This is better than any of those other chains that you just mentioned
Yeah, well, like I said, they're not a huge chain. They're around but not I like the looks of their cheese pizza
ooh yeah and they've got nice oh I found a map here they're pretty popular over
here uh-huh show me locations I'm clicking on it yeah don't allow yeah
they're all oh they're big on the East Coast yeah they're clustered over here
looks like the closest one to using Colorado yeah and I'm not going there
Arizona's a little closer, buddy.
Uh, is it?
No, they're about the same.
Yeah.
I bet it would take me the same amount of time
to get to either one of those.
Ronnie could scoot down to Arizona pretty quick.
He always is in Arizona.
When he's not home, what he does is he opens all his doors
and windows and then he drives out of the driveway
and then he drives straight.
(laughing)
He drives straight down to Arizona.
Stop.
Hey!
It's a return to a theme of earlier.
You gotta cycle back.
Oh my goodness.
Ronnie would not appreciate the trolling if I wasn't continuing the trolling.
This is true.
Yeah.
So, anyway, it looks like they've managed to stay out of Cuba, but they're pretty close.
Oh my goodness, Cuba.
What?
Nothing.
Some of the things that come out of your mouth. Well, they are I'm looking at the map. I managed to stay out of Cuba
Who thinks about that?
When I look at the map, I'm just noticing how close Miami and Cuba are
I mean, I don't think about it all the time because I don't live in that part of the country
Okay, but you could basically throw a rock and hit some poor Cuban guy
way the Cuban could throw the rock and hit some dude in Miami. For sure the Everglades though,
if you're if you're riding your little fan boat through the Everglades some some guy in Cuba
could wing a good one up there and whack you right in the head. No? Too soon? Why do you?
You're good.
All right. What else you got? Anything else? Are we done? I mean-
I think that's it.
We've hit all the shower notes.
We've ran out of friends.
Well, we haven't taken any shots at Clay or Chidgey.
Do you want to you want to go ahead and line them up while you're at it?
Well, no. Oh, my God.
Well, you know what?
What? No, it just I know I don't want to take any shots at either.
I was going to say, oh, wow, this cat looks like mine.
Oh, over one year old.
No, never mind.
I am looking at, so I told you I'd get those emails.
Yes. You know, saying this could be the cat that you found
and it's never the cat that we found.
By the way, got any updates on that front?
We did go to the vet and we told the truth, Vic.
We said a very irresponsible person gave us this cat.
OK, continue.
They didn't do anything to it.
They didn't neuter it. They didn't take care of it.
But they gave us this cat and asked us if we could have the cat.
And we said, yes.
And now the cats are, so please start the process.
So they started the process.
So basically the cat has had the first round of vaccines, this cat that was given to us,
and it's going to get neutered in about a week from now it's going to get neutered.
And then it will get its...
It can finally come in the house.
Well, they don't want to do that until it gets the next round of vaccines, which is
the following week.
Oh, okay.
So in theory, it's still got two and a half more weeks
in the garage, but I don't think so,
because when that cat gets neutered,
it's gonna have to wear the cone of shame.
And I don't, my wife was really good
about going out in the garage.
You really honestly need to keep him
where you can keep an eye on him.
Exactly, right, exactly.
And so, yeah, my wife was really good
about setting up the garage as safe as possible,
but there's still so many nooks and crannies
that that cat likes to go into out there.
It is not gonna be safe with that cone of shame on.
Yeah. And so at that point, the cat's going to have to come into the house.
Now, the good news is the two cats have already been smelling each other
and meowing at each other quite a bit underneath the garage door.
So they're getting acclimated. That's good.
They're getting acclimated.
So that part of it's not going to be nearly as bad as it could be.
I don't think. Yeah.
Whether they'll like each other once they get full on contact with each other
still remains to be seen.
But this is the process that you have to go through.
You introduce cats to each other gently. Yeah.
You don't just wing them at each other and say, hey,
"Hey, let's see how this goes."
(laughs)
Right.
So anyway, that part of it will be substantially easier.
And so anyway, the process is happening.
It's looking a lot better.
This little guy is so playful, he's so funny.
And he's definitely younger than we thought.
We thought he was over a year old when we first got him,
but he still has some kitten tendencies.
He's probably just under one.
He's probably between six to eight months to one year
or something like that.
He's probably way more than six months,
but he's probably not a year.
And he still pounces like a kitten.
He's so funny.
He is very playful,
but you can still tell he's got some kitten in him.
That's cool.
And just the way he responds to people,
the way he meows at people,
as though his life is ending
if they don't respond to his every need.
You know how cats can do.
Yeah.
But anyway, it's working out pretty well.
I feel a lot better about it now than I did
when it seemed like it was gonna be 90 days
before our vet would touch him.
Yeah.
And by the way, I went to the same vet.
I went to our normal vet.
I had called them, but I didn't identify myself
when I was like, "Hey, we found this cat.
What's the process?"
Oh, that's fortunate.
Yeah, but the thing is they can see my phone number on the...
So what I don't know is if they remembered that
and they knew it was me,
because I think I talked to the same person.
Well, honestly speaking, I mean,
maybe they actually want to do the right thing
by the cats and they need you to lie to them
so that they can cover their bases.
That's exactly what I'm thinking is like,
They know full well that the odds of people not being able to help a cat go up immensely
when they're presented with this huge challenge of waiting 90 days.
Yeah. Especially if they already have another cat.
So I think I think they just they don't want people to steal cats.
They don't want they definitely want anybody would want a cat to go to back to its rightful owner.
If there is an owner looking for the cat, the cat should go back there.
Yeah. And even though you and I might judge those people morally a little bit
for not taking care of the cat in the first place.
Mm hmm. Not even getting it vaccinated, not even getting it fixed,
not even getting it chipped and then letting it roam around outside
as a young, young cat, a very young cat.
And the fact that nobody seems to have tried looking for it.
It doesn't seem like it.
We had posters out because it's not like you've made it hard for them to find it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Not at all. In fact, the website that I registered him with is the shelter
that all the other places get their information from about lost cats.
>> JOSHUA Right.
>> PHILIP Right.
>> CHIP Right.
So anyway, if somebody was looking for him, they could find him if they really wanted
to.
If there is an owner that's worrying about him, they're basically sitting there doing
nothing.
They're just sitting there going, "Oh, I wonder where Kitty is.
Oh, I guess we'll never know."
>> JOSHUA Right.
>> CHIP But that's the amount of care that they've
put into this cat already.
So do I feel bad thinking that there might be somebody out there wondering what happened
to the cat?
Yeah, of course I do.
But also, I also feel like this cat now has a family that's going to take care of it and
it's going to be part of the family.
>> JOSHUA That's right.
It would be my opinion they failed the cat and they've lost their privileges.
Yeah, right. And that's easy for us to say, but I genuinely do feel a little bit that way.
I just, I can't imagine. Like, if one of my cats actually went missing, like...
When we had Bella, and we'd only had her maybe not even for a full month yet,
there was one time that somebody didn't get the door closed and she got out.
And the cat was only missing for like 12 hours.
And within that 12 hours,
I had already papered our neighborhood
and a few adjacent neighborhoods with flyers
that I just printed up right on the computer.
The wife and I and one of the kids
had spent the entire day out looking for the cat and stuff.
And it just...
Yeah, it kills you.
You wanna know.
I don't feel like whoever owns this cat.
I feel like they failed the cat.
Well, let me just posit to you one more piece of information, Vic.
One of the reasons I don't want my doors opening unexpectedly on this house is I don't want my cats disappearing.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, I definitely get that.
Like they may not run away on purpose, but if a door is left open, they're going to go out it.
And if I'm not home, they might. Who knows what will happen?
Like, true. No, I definitely get that.
Midnight did get out recently when he,
when we first brought this little cat into the garage,
he knew his little buddy was out there
and he's never been outside of this house
that I can remember except for in a cat carrier.
So he doesn't know how the house works.
So he tried to get out the front door to go get to that cat.
Yeah.
'Cause actually I think Midnight has stood there
and seen us open the garage door before.
So he knows that it leads to the front.
And so anyway, he ran out of the house
to go get to his little buddy
and it's the only time he's ever tried
to run out of the house.
And he had just been sniffing under the door.
They had been meowing at each other.
And all of a sudden, my wife opened the door and he she left it open too long.
She wasn't paying attention. I say that I don't. OK.
I'll edit that out because I don't actually know, but that's how I took it.
Fingers are being pointed.
They're definitely being pointed.
They're being pointed at Ronnie Ronnie, you son of a bitch.
Anyway, the cat got out and he got in the bushes
and he finally came pushing through the hedge.
with his head covered in spiderwebs.
It was kind of hilarious.
And I put him back inside and he hasn't tried again since.
But that would be a nightmare because he's not prepared.
Like he would be lost.
I mean, could he find his way back? Maybe.
I don't know. I don't want him getting run over.
Anyway, the whole point is take care of your cats.
I think we said that last time.
I'm just going to PSA that every time from now on.
Even when Peter comes back and I think it's a good PSA.
Yeah, it's a good PSA.
Okay, that's enough.
All right.
So it's time to push the button.
Hey, do you have any PSAs for your friend Ronnie Lutz?
No, I think you covered all the PSAs for Ronnie Lutz.
I'm going to let you have it.
Okay.
And I'm going to push the button on that note.
Sounds good.
I'm pushing a button too.
Tell your friends.